hey bro I hope you brought your balls
with you
a heheheheh you know I do I would never
forget to polish my big-ass balls
damn bro you crazy do you seriously
polish your balls every [ __ ] time
they it's what I got to do got to stay
ahead of the competition so where's this
new teammate you spoke of bro
I'm telling you guys she is so [ __ ]
amazing she told me herself with her on
our bowling team we would be unstoppable
welcome it took the damn Mindy yo pay yo
they [ __ ] does mean a face I see away
the cows a flock which let's go stop a
OS and come at come and Mindy baby get
you big ass over here
alright dudes who's ready to go bowling
I brought my favorite wall
hey Knuckles um how is it going oh you
know the usual
hey Manik I know the last time we played
I didn't hit a single pin but today is
going to be different I stayed up all
night practicing and even bought new
balls
my great grandfather Athair he begged me
to stop but I did not listen I just told
him to suck my big sweaty balls he just
doesn't understand Pro Bowlers like us
hey Manik after we are done we should
stop by my house and beat his [ __ ]
pest Knuckles stop it what did you just
say to me [ __ ] I will [ __ ] beat your
ass nobody talks back to Knuckles the
cool Echidna I'm really sorry I should
have told you sooner from this day forth
you are no longer on our bowling team
what the [ __ ] Manik we are best friends
you can't do this to me please I beg you
could you even get in my place
haha so I hear you're the one who can't
play with balls how about you step aside
little boy leave this to the
professionals so that's how it is I've
been completely replaced KKnux wait
please just give me a minute to explain
you know Manic sometimes when I lay
awake at night I think about how cool it
would be if we ever won the national
bowling championships but I guess in the
end that's all it was just a dream so
long [ __ ]
wait Knuckles Knuckles come back I'm
sorry
Dominus what W does fro he's on let's go
you
[Applause]
holy [ __ ] is that who I think it is that
looks like the Sonic Underground aren't
they like famous or some [ __ ]
I think you're right Randy I heard that
they're the thirty-eighth best bowling
team in the state
excuse me you're Sonic the Hedgehog
right do you think I could touch your
ball your bowling balls
I mean son let me tell you something
that my uncle has always told me learn
how to play with your own balls before
you go around playing with everyone
else's when you have more experience
with balls come back to me I will be
waiting big boy hey your Uncle Chuck
aren't you could I have an autograph I'm
a huge fan of wedge of course a yoga
Nevaeh no Dourif is where it sucks as my
infamous looky for yo al wife's car it
is with years around who stink-ass a run
into me fast of course a it's going to
cost you 50 bucks you have to be
[ __ ] if you'd think that would stop
me you're Sonic Underground correct the
aisle that you rented out for the night
is ready we hope that it is for you
lacking only the best for the 38 best
bowling team in the whole [ __ ] state
not bad
think you could go get me and my crew
some nachos while you're here well well
well if it isn't the Sonic Underground
Robotnik what the hell are you doing
here and no it can't be
so which is remember me Knuckles you
traitor you traitorous son of a [ __ ]
will [ __ ] kill you you shut up fat
boy you're the ones who get him out of
your bowling team you all left him with
nowhere to go so we decided to take him
in and make him one of us
how many times do I have to tell you
[ __ ] you only get to talk when I tell
you to
Knuckles tell me this isn't true you
wouldn't really join Robotnik's bowling
team what happened to bros before hos
balls before boobs does that mean
nothing to you that's right we found
this poor red man crying in a Long John
Silver's barking crying about how his
best friends don't care about him
anymore we had to buy him a plate of
fried shrimp and french fries just to
calm him down
he back the [ __ ] up I told you to stop
grabbing my [ __ ] Pez and I already
told you that as long as you're part of
my team you're my property got it just
like those two [ __ ] over there yeah
you have to learn your place just like
the rest of us [ __ ] or do you just not
care about getting revenge on those who
wronged you
yo dr. Robotnik I gotta ask what exactly
are you doing here
it takes a big set of balls stepping
into our territory I think we all know
that my bowling team is the one who owns
this side of town is that so
I have to apologize to you then me and
my crew were just passing by somehow I
don't believe that you know tell you see
so territory in going to keep your
[ __ ] a sweet little calm down Uncle
Chuck it's not worth getting into a
fight over you don't want to spend the
night in jail again do you yet come your
[ __ ] tits old man let me guess you're
here because you want to challenge my
team to a bullying match
I can't imagine you coming here for any
other reason than to play with your
balls you know meet well Sonic the
Hedgehog
I just can't get enough of touching big
balls I'm afraid that we are going to
have to decline my crew came here to
practice not rape you I was afraid you
would say that you fat blue [ __ ] that's
why I brought something with me if you
refused to play with my balls this man
will be killed and it will be all your
fault oh my God
daddy what have they done to you damn
you Robotnik damn you and your evil ways
you won't get away with this many men be
my baby girl is that
I can't see anything but calls up my
blackett hurry I need you to jump up and
down and slap your big boobs together
let me hear them slapping against your
16 year old body so I can know you're
all right of course daddy it seems
you've got in your way Robotnik will
play but if we win you let mine DS dad
Bo glad you see it my way
if I win your little band of [ __ ] are
banned from ever stepping foot in this
bowling alley again bro were not
actually going to bowl against him are
we have to my green bro if we don't mind
these dad will be raped or worse killed
is this one good no that's a bit too
small you're going to need a bigger one
than that that's the first time somebody
has ever told me I have small balls ha
ha ha ha Sleet I don't understand why
are you being so nice to him he's
Robotnik's [ __ ]
you saw Herald botanique rammed his butt
cheeks this guy just stood there and
took it then go we're all Robotnik's
[ __ ] Robotnik grabs your butt cheeks
about four times a day
the real question here Dingo is why do
you want to believe someone who didn't
do anything to you
I'm sorry Sleet since he's so much
smaller than me I guess for the first
time ever I just feel a lot what like
you have power suck my balls Dingo
you're just being a big bully I'm sorry
Sleet please don't be mad I don't want
to fight with my best friend I'll just
grab my balls and go oh yeah did I
forget to tell you you're not part of
the bowling team anymore you've been
replaced by Knuckles Robotnik says that
boy really knows his balls also you've
been demoted to water boy so go over
there and stand with the swat-bots
or better yet go get us some nachos you
know Robotnik loves himself some nachos
hi um I don't mean to be a bother but
you're Bart levy right the richest man
live Sonic the Hedgehog's boyfriend I'm
so happy that I could meet you
you
oh I didn't see you standing there what
do you want I was just wondering if I
couldn't have an autograph No
hey Knuckles have you seen where Dingle
what I sent him to buy nachos like an
hour ago I saw him taking a dump in the
bathroom a little while ago he sounded
like he was crying
ha crying I believe it he always was a
little [ __ ]
what the [ __ ] is that him over at the
food stand can I have three large nachos
with extra cheese dip please oh and
don't forget the jalapenos Robotnik
would beat my ass if I forgot about
those no I said extra cheese dip why
aren't you listening to me
yeah I'm willing to pay extra for the
extra cheese dip really pile that [ __ ]
on there that's good that's really good
Dingo Dingo is that you what the hell
happened to your pants
oh hey there Sleet I'm vining knockos
exactly like you asked me to you're not
mad at me anymore are you I just want to
know why you're [ __ ] naked you see I
took off my clothes
I felt that since I wasn't on the team
anymore it wasn't right for me to wear
them well put them back on nobody wants
to see your big [ __ ] ass
why the [ __ ] you crying I should be the
one crying [ __ ] I'm crying because
you're yelling at me
all I wanted was to Bowl you know it's
my dream to be a pro bowler we all have
dreams Dingo nobody gives a [ __ ] about a
stupid one like yours my dream is not
stupid the only thing more stupid than
your dream is the fact that you're
buying nachos naked I mean are you going
to shove them up your ass should I go
get my camera
oh sweet I'm so confused you said I
wasn't on the team anymore
so I took off my uniform now you're
telling me to put it back on that
doesn't make any sense what do you want
from me I want you to go home Dingo
Dingo I'm so sorry I didn't mean it
Dingo please stop crying
you